[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries did cholera affect most?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["USA", "Italy", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not among the actors who have won both an Oscar and a Razzie?", "correct_answer": "Gregory Peck", "incorrect_answers": ["Charleston Heston", "Roberto Benigni", "Marlon Brando"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1996 film, Courage Under Fire, starring Denzel Washington and Meg Ryan, was partially filmed in a United States Desert..", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1930s, ehe Dust Bowl directly affected these four US states.", "correct_answer": "Texas, Oklahoma, New Mexico, and Colorado", "incorrect_answers": ["Oklahoma, Kansas, Missouri, and Iowa", "Texas, Oklahoma, Missouri, and Kansas", "Texas. Oklahoma, Kansas, and Iowa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, and John Adams were all avid players of this game.", "correct_answer": "Marbles", "incorrect_answers": ["Hide and seek", "Scrabble", "Monopoly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After the car accident in the film Fight Club, the car is on its roof and Tyler Durden climbs out of which car door?", "correct_answer": "passenger side", "incorrect_answers": ["rear passenger side", "rear driver side", "driver side"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venomous mammals do exist, although they are very rare. Which of these mammals is venomous?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["European Mole", "Cuban Solenodon", "Platypus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the ratio of a circles circumference to its diameter?", "correct_answer": "Pi", "incorrect_answers": ["i", "e", "log(x)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Talladega Nights, Ricky drives his car into a buggy and a policeman.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ireland, New Zealand and Japan are three countries with very high consumption of this drink.", "correct_answer": "Tea", "incorrect_answers": ["Brandy", "Coffee", "Coca-cola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Baseball player Alexander Rodriguez, who became the youngest player ever to hit 500 home runs, started his professional career with this team.", "correct_answer": "Seattle Mariners", "incorrect_answers": ["New York Yankees", "Detroit Tigers", "Texas Rangers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie, directed by Stanley Kubrick, stars Malcolm McDowell as Alex DeLarge.", "correct_answer": "A Clockwork Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["A Backward Peach", "A Future of  Red", "Soylent Green"]}]